[Music]
hello NEX agency and all our Muslim
colleagues
Salameh or puasa i am delighted to
launch our very own electronic
submission tool applause
the next agency and Manulife development
teams and worked diligently over the
past twelve months to launch applause
despite many challenges
not on my MCU the development teams in
Malaysia Philippines and Vietnam all
deserve a huge applause for the
dedication to completing a project on
time our launch starts with a pilot
based on mate worth it continues to a
phase to launch in July that includes
Eden refine you wallet additional
products and writers in August real
boost to another 200 super users and by
October you will have a grand launch all
members of Nick's agency beneath us we
get a paperless process and it's faster
than easier available on any device any
time I strongly urge all members of
mixings gear up and familiarize yourself
the new normal of doing business
digitally with next agency anything is
possible
[Music]
hello Becks agency today is the launch
of people's and I'd like to congratulate
the first 100 and bascinets of using
this new model on behalf of insurance in
today's launch we'll also be sharing
creepy things on terms of the benefits
of using people's number one the more
use that you'll be experiencing number
two the sales campaign to accelerate
your submission and third the
underwriting Jaime that you'll be
experiencing because you're an equals
user without further ado let's look into
the month of Evo's and see what benefits
you can beat ladies and gentlemen from
the screen you will see that the
benefits that you are able to use during
the I post experiences that it is a
complete propose and apply process you
access it using your single sign-on menu
life email or 365 and when you enter
there are three products are really
available they are namely the menu
secure menu link premier and menu link
essential series coupled with each in
writers that comes along with it it is a
true paperless experience whereby you
impress all customers with the
electronic signature electronic payment
facility and more importantly the
underwriting priority Lane and all of
you will be experiencing when you submit
this case electronically so go all out
and use this he paused to impress and
bring in the business in terms of the
campaign's that will help you accelerate
the electronic submission process we
have two incentives that will definitely
excite you number one to own a totally
free Apple iPad with 20 gigabytes of
data plan for over two years all you
need to do is achieve sixty thousand
ringgit worth of a PE
issue before the 31st of July is 2020
not only that for every I posted
submission that you do you will also
earn 25 ringing extra on every case that
you have submitted and get it issued
before 31st of July okay so go all out
next agency I would like to remind you
while you are using a pause it is also
important that you are able to submit
efficiently of the quality business when
you meet up with your customers
therefore it is compulsory for you to
attend Ipoh screening scheduled by the
company I suggest you look up the
calendar that is available in menu learn
and register yourself and quickly learn
all the skills required to use I pause
now before I end the presentation on the
launch of I pause all next agency
members especially the first 100
ambassadors are finally experiencing
business on the go you are able to use a
pause at any time and it probably even
on any device should you need help
giving your experience with a pause
during this pilot process I encourage
all of you to contact us for a system
based on the telephone number and email
of the digital launch you may also
connect via whatsapp group until then I
hope that all of you enjoy the
experience of our very new ethos and
then the launch of evolve is now
official I encourage everyone to go ha
impress all potential recruits and
customers but more importantly I will
see you in the steps of success of
becoming the next any arts
[Music]
we are living in a world of constant
connectivity as we strive in our daily
lives the role of technology will change
the way we transact introducing a pose
the future of virtual platforms for
agents and customers alike Evo's is
designed to be an accessible secure and
efficient platform for agents to
effectively perform their operations at
their convenience of their fingertips to
start open browser and login with menu
like o 365 account the quick filling out
of the customers details will generate a
profile that can be accessed whenever
you need to produce an accurate position
that will be displayed for verification
and payment all within minutes the
proposal module is a comprehensive and
intelligent sales and marketing staging
tool allowing agents to present
professional and comprehensive solutions
to their perspective customers once
customers need has been identified the
proposal will instantaneously be
generated for agent to recommend it to
them Evos is designed with the latest
technology in mind this allows customers
to confirm their purchase of a plan
immediately and begin a credit or debit
card payment all in real time
eople scripts proficient agents who
desire 24/7 availability from point of
sales to offering manualized solutions
anytime anywhere while simplifying their
day-to-day work processes and to end
business processes meet simple
people's clarity connectivity pretty
you
hi next agency glad to meet you all
virtually I know you have waited very
long for a post Malaysia to go life and
now he posed a girl live on 24th April
now let's get start to see how a pose
looks and feel
that's not you can use any device
locking with this URL because this is a
web-based application equals word space
with Google Chrome and Safari compared
to other browser working with your man
alive all 3-6-5 emu and password once
login you can see customer pick click on
the plus sign to start creating your
customer profile you will come to a
customer dashboard after enter all basic
info here you can see proposals and
application proposals here is product
illustration and application is the
application form click on proposal click
on plus sign to create proposal first
one you will see only three products
select a product that meet customer
needs and click create proposal select
primary issue start creating your plan
when complete click Next you can view
your proposal here in table or chart
format if confirmed no changes click on
preview final proposal you will see the
product illustration here you can email
or print out the product illustration
for your customer if they want a copy of
it click apply to start filling up the
application form
please complete all the sections one by
one on your left customer need to sign
and confirm on the signature then
followed by agent signature proceed to a
payment through up the credit card
detail and submit payment after payment
done and back to submission screen you
will see submission message policy
number and payment amount this is not
final yet you must click on submit to
complete your final submission how do
you know your proposal has been
submitted successfully you will see the
message on top application is submitted
successfully for confirmation to check
the application status click back to
application list
application list allows you to see the
status of the applications that you have
submitted customer will receive instant
notification via email on temporary
cover application resolve and paper
receipt once
agent has submitted the case
successfully alright that's it from me
it's so easy and user-friendly I shall
see you in my a post training soon thank
you stay safe and take care good bye
[Music]
[Applause]